Всем привет, это Бетт. Вы здесь,
поздравляю! Вы стали свидетелями
запуска децентрализованной сети,
первого в истории краудсорсингового парачейн-
аукциона на Kusama, канареечной сети Polkadot
Теперь, конечно, канареечаня сеть Acala,
Karura, находится на переднем плане этого
беспрецедентного старта.
Поддержав Karura crowdloan здесь
вы посожете нам
в запуске DeFi центра Kusama,
что позволит вам торговать, стейкать, выдавать кредиты
и брать займы
и зарабатывайте на цифровых
активах.
But of course no promises, expect chaos
and expect
Karura. Now let me run you through
number of ways to participate in the
Karura crowdloan.
If you have a referral link, you can use
that to join the event directly,
otherwise you can just go to our website
acala.network to participate.
There are three ways we recommend to
participate in the event
to maximize your rewards, but it's
permissionless event
so you can well make your own judgment
on how you would like to participate.
Well, obviously, you can participate just
directly on this website
using polkadot.js extension or
you can participate via our partner
exchanges
or via our partner mobile wallets.
We will continue to add official
partners to the list
as they become ready. Please, do reach out
to the exchanges and
wallets for any support questions.
Before you start though, do check if you
have the extension
installed and also have some free KSM
in your wallet to participate.
The Karura crowdloan will airdrop a
minimum of
12 KAR rewards for 1 KSM contributed in
the event.
Okay, now let's connect to the extension.
Please read and accept the terms and
conditions regarding the event and also
the privacy policy,
before you proceed. Your acceptance will
be a
signed message from your current account.
It won't be sent on chain
and won't cost you anything.
If you have contributed to the event
already, you shall see a balance on top
and estimated KAR rewards. Then just put
in the KSM
contribution amount. Notice the lease
period
is 48 weeks, so if Karura successfully
wins the auction,
ваши KSM будут заблокированы на 48 недель
и 30% наград будут доступны к перемещению,
по остальным - вестинг.
Вы можете участвовать несколько раз
в течение всего crowdloan-периода
Если вы используете реферальную ссылку,
реферальный код будет заполнен автоматически.
Иначе вы можете просто взять код из
нашего сообщества в discord
и вы получите 5% бонус.
Теперь вы можете просто
отправить транзакцию взноса в
релейную сеть Kusama.
Это может занять несколько секунд, так как оно
ждет завершения и подтверждения Kusama
вашу транзакцию
с вашим взносом
И это всё! Пожалуйста, поделитесь
своим превосходным достижением в социальных сетях.
В любом случае,
ещё раз поздравляем и благодарим вас за
создание истории
вместе с Karura!